Hi Annie, everyone. Judge Andrew
Napolitano here for Judging Freedom.
Today is Monday, December 8th, 2025.
John Kiriakou, former CIA officer, will
be with us in just a moment on the CIA's
tortures and on its crimes.
But first this. History tells us every
market eventually falls. Currencies
collapse. And look at where we are now,
38 trillion in national debt. Stocks at
record highs defying gravity. So, what
happens next? Groceries, gas, housing,
everything's going up. And this dollar,
it buys less every day. When the system
breaks, your stocks won't save you and
your dollars won't either. But one thing
will. Gold. I've said it on my show for
years. Gold survives collapse. Central
bankers know this and billionaires know
it. That's why they're buying more. Is
[music] it too late to buy or is it just
the right time? Call my friends at Lear
Capital to find out. Ask questions, get
the free information. [music]
There's no pressure and that's why I buy
my gold and silver from Lear. And right
now, you can get up to [music] $20,000
in bonus metals with a qualified
purchase. Call 800-511-4620
or go to Learjudgenap.com [music]
today.
John Kiriakou, welcome here, uh my dear
friend. Thank you so much. So good to
see you again. Well, thank you. It's
nice to see you. We've known each other
for a long time. You were an
intelligence analyst and an operations
officer for the CIA.
You received numerous medals and
citations
commending your work.
Yet when you decided to when you learned
of CIA torture and decided to expose it,
for that you were prosecuted, entered a
guilty plea, and spent 23 months in a
federal prison. To be clear,
you went to jail not for torturing but
for exposing
the torture, for revealing it.
Yes.
>> opinion, in an age of few heroes,
you are the genuine article.
>> Oh, thank you so much. Thank you. It's
really a great pleasure to see you
again. I'm happy to be here.
Why did you
What did you observe and why did you
decide to reveal it?
>> [snorts]
>> It started in May of 2002. I had just
returned from Pakistan to CIA
headquarters. In Pakistan, I had been
the chief of CIA counterterrorism
operations and I had led a series of
successful, very successful raids that
resulted in the capture of Abu Zubaydah
and dozens upon dozens of other Al-Qaeda
fighters at every level. I went back to
headquarters to start my next assignment
as the chief of counterintelligence
in the Osama bin Laden unit called Alec
Station. And a senior officer just
casually approached me in the cafeteria
and asked if I wanted to be, his words,
"certified in the use of enhanced
interrogation techniques." I had never
heard the term before.
And uh I asked him what he was talking
about and he said excitedly, "We're
going to start getting rough with these
guys." I said, "Well, what does that
mean?"
And then he explained these 10 different
techniques to me. I said, "That sounds
like a torture program." He said, "No,
it was not torture. The president had
approved it and the Justice Department
had approved it." I sought the counsel
of a very senior CIA officer
who confirmed my belief that this was a
torture program and was likely illegal
besides being immoral and unethical.
And so I went back down to the CIA's
Counterterrorism Center and I said,
"This is not for me. I think it's
illegal and I want no part of it."
That's when the CIA began to turn on me.
I had a very dear friend also working in
the Counterterrorism Center who happened
to be a brigadier general in the Army
Reserve and a psychiatrist.
And he said to me, "You know, they call
you the human rights guy behind your
back."
I said, "I don't care."
He said, "You know, that's not a
compliment." And I said, "Listen,
I'm on the right side of this and they
are not." I ended up becoming the
executive assistant to the CIA's deputy
director.
And in that position, I was able to see
literally everything that the CIA was
doing around the world. And I was seeing
reporting coming back from the secret
site where Abu Zubaydah was being
tortured.
And I was heartened to know that I
wasn't the only one who had opposed this
torture. I expected that somebody would
go public with it.
And nobody did. I ended up leaving the
CIA two years later and went into the
private sector. Finally in 2007,
Brian Ross called me from ABC News
and said that he had a source who said
that I had tortured Abu Zubaydah. I said
that was absolutely untrue. I was the
only person who was kind to Abu
Zubaydah.
And he said, "Well, you're welcome to
come on the show and defend yourself." I
had never met a journalist before. I had
never spoken to a journalist before and
I didn't know that that was an old
journalism trick.
So,
I told him I'd think about it. Later
that week, uh President Bush
gave a press conference in which he
looked right in the in the camera and
said, "We do not torture."
I knew that was a lie.
And then later in the week, as he was
walking from the South Portico of the
White House to the helicopter to go to
Camp David,
a reporter shouted a question
and he turned and he said, "Well, if
there is torture, it's the result of a
rogue CIA officer."
And I told my wife at the time, who was
also a senior CIA officer,
"Brian Ross's source is at the White
House and they're going to pin this on
me." And so I decided to give him his
interview and I decided that no matter
what he asked me, I would tell the truth
and just let the cards fall. And that's
what I did.
And did you tell them
what was being done without getting too
graphic to Abu Zubaydah and did you
reveal the identity
of the person or people who were doing
it?
Um I did reveal what the techniques
were. Yes, I did not reveal the
identity, but then later on,
not realizing that John Brennan had
asked the FBI to reopen the case against
me seen secretly.
I didn't know that my emails were being
intercepted, my phone calls were being
intercepted. There were teams of FBI
agents following me everywhere. This
went on for three years.
And in the summer of 2008, a journalist
emailed me
and said, "Do you know where I could
find
John who's mentioned on page 165 of your
first book?" And I said, and this was
the crime. I said, "Oh, I think you're
talking about John Smith."
I said, "I don't know what happened to
him. He's probably retired and living
somewhere in Virginia."
And they got me because I confirmed the
name of a former colleague. That name
was never made public.
But they got me. They charged me with
violating the Intelligence Identities
Protection Act of 1981
and they charged me with three counts of
espionage. Now,
you know as well as I do, espionage can
be a death penalty charge.
They offered me, they made their first
offer in a proffer meeting, of 45 years
in prison.
Oh my lord. One of the one of the Obama
assistant US attorneys said to me in
this meeting,
"Take the deal, Mr. Kiriakou, and you
may live to meet your grandchildren."
So, I knew I was in for a fight.
And what what happened from there? How
did it get down from 45 years to 23
months?
Well, I I was fortunate in that
this was enough of a public issue that I
attracted A-list criminal defense
attorneys. My lead attorney was a was a
to use the Washington Post's words, a
legal giant, a titan. His name was Plato
Cacheris. Oh, I know I don't know if
Plato's around anymore, but I know I
know. Yes.
>> away a couple of years ago, but he
really was a giant. And then Plato's
partner, Bob Trout at Trout Cacheris, as
well as Anking Up in Straus's
director of white-collar defense, uh
Wait a minute. Did you pick Plato
because he's Greek? Yes.
>> [laughter]
>> When I was when I was in college, my
godfather, who owned a restaurant here
in in Alexandria, Virginia, told me, he
introduced me to Plato, who was having
lunch there one day, and he said, "God
forbid." I was a teenager. He said, "God
forbid you should be in trouble someday,
but if you ever are, you have to hire
this man, Plato Cacheris. And I said,
"Okay." And I kind of put it in the back
of my mind.
And then
30 years later,
I find myself in trouble. And so I
called Plato Cacheris.
And he obviously negotiated a plea deal.
I think you were sentenced to 3 years
and you served 23 months, if I have that
correctly.
>> exactly right. I was sentenced to 2 and
1/2 and I served 23 months. Right.
Right. Right. And those heavier absurd
charges, all the charges were absurd,
but the heavy ones, the ones that
carried 45 years, those were all
dropped.
>> They were all dropped. And you know,
that's that's kind of the thing. We're
hearing a lot these days about
weaponization, the weaponization of
intelligence. And this is what
weaponization looks like. They knew I
hadn't committed espionage, but in
discovery, we were given
a series of letters. There was a letter
from John Brennan to then Attorney
General Eric Holder saying, "Charge him
with espionage." And Holder wrote back
and said, "My people don't think he
committed espionage."
And then Brennan wrote back and said,
"Charge him anyway and make him defend
himself." And that's what they did. And
then as soon as I went bankrupt,
they dropped the espionage charges.
Wow.
Um does the CIA regularly torture?
Well, this is one of those things where
they tell us, "No, we don't torture
anymore. We can't prove it. You're going
to have to take our word for it." I I
want to believe that they don't torture
anymore. I was very very proud to play a
role
in passage of the McCain-Feinstein
Amendment. You know, 6 weeks before
I was released from prison, I called my
wife. She I was allowed to speak to her
every other day for 15 minutes. And so I
called her and I said, "How was your
day?" She said, "It was great." I said,
"Really? Why was it so great?"
And she said, "Because the Senate
torture report was released today and it
proved that everything you said was
true. And John McCain got up on the
floor of the Senate
and said that had it not been for me and
my revelations, the American people
would never have known what the
government was doing in their name."
I want to believe that the CIA is not
torturing. Torture is against the law.
It's unequivocal.
But it's one of those cases where we're
just going to have to take their word
for it.
Was the the torture of which you're
aware or which you reported
the only torture of which you were aware
or was it rampant in those days? I mean,
the subsequent head of the CIA,
a woman named Gina Haspel, her nickname
given to her by your former colleagues
was Bloody Gina. Why would they have
given her a nickname like that?
Yeah, it was Bloody Gina.
It was because when she was senior
officer in the CIA's Counterterrorism
Center, she flew out to the secret site
just so that she could sit in and watch
a torture session.
What normal person would do something
like that? To answer your question more
directly, Your Honor,
torture was rampant. And it wasn't just
torture at the hands of CIA officers. It
was CIA officers training
officers of other intelligence services
in the use of torture. For example,
Craig Murray, the former British
Ambassador to Uzbekistan, had a meeting
while he was ambassador, had a meeting
at the Uzbek intelligence service. He
could hear a man screaming
while he was carrying on this meeting.
And he got up and against
the admonitions of his uh
of his Uzbek partners, went into a room
where a man was being boiled in oil. And
he said that he saw the man's skin come
off of it come off of his body like like
removing a glove.
He reported that to his foreign ministry
and they told him to
take the cable down
and be promoted to Ambassador to Denmark
or
go to the press
and be under arrest.
And he went to the press. His life was
ruined. His career was ruined.
But he's a champion of human rights.
Wow.
Uh he's been on the uh program
uh a number of times and I did not know
of that
uh horrific event that he observed and
of his
uh of his act of courage. You said that
the CIA was uh following you and
monitoring you.
I mean, you formerly followed and
monitored people. How
How could they
How How could they elude your awareness
of what they were doing?
>> And I have to tell you, too, I'm I'm
embarrassed to say I was a CIA
surveillance instructor
and I never noticed it. I never noticed
it because it was right here in Northern
Virginia
and I wouldn't have any reason to be
under surveillance. There was one
incident. My mother's sister died in
Western Pennsylvania
and her funeral coincided with a
a
a hearing a legal hearing that I had on
custody. I was getting divorced.
And
I drove up to Pennsylvania. I went to
the funeral. And then I thought, "I have
a free day. I'm going to go look at my
grandparents' old house and then I'm
going to go to the cemetery and put some
flowers on their graves." So I went up
there
and I parked my car in front of the
house and I was just sitting there
looking at it and there was a car behind
me. So I rolled my window down and I
waved for him to go around me.
And he didn't go around me.
And so I went up to the next
intersection, made an illegal U-turn
to go toward the cemetery and he made
the illegal U-turn. And I thought, "Oh,
that's not normal. Something's up." So I
went to the cemetery. He followed me
into the cemetery. I parked the car near
my grandparents' graves and I walked up
to his car and I said, "What's up?"
And he took off.
So I called my wife, who was also a CIA
surveillance instructor, and I said,
"I'm under surveillance up here. I'm
sure of it."
And she said, "It has to be
a uh
it has to be a private investigator
hired by your first wife. Maybe they're
just looking to see
whatever they can find."
And I said, "Yeah, it it has to be." It
turned out what it was was the FBI. They
didn't know my aunt had died and they
thought I was running to Canada. They
thought that I had spotted them and I
was running to Canada, which was
ludicrous. I have five children.
But um that was the only time I noticed
them and it was because they were so
obvious.
Does the CIA commit crimes besides
torture?
Oh, every day.
Every day. You know, I I say this a lot,
but it it bears repeating. A CIA
psychiatrist once told me that the CIA
actively seeks to hire people who have
sociopathic tendencies. That is not
sociopaths. Sociopaths have no
conscience. And as a result, they blow
right through a polygraph exam. They're
impossible to control because they
they're unable to feel guilt or remorse.
People who have sociopathic tendencies
do feel guilt or remorse. They do react
during polygraph exams, but they're
happy to break the law because we're the
good guys. I'll give you an example. In
uh in the application process, the the
instructor said to us, uh
uh if you were you were a CIA officer in
the field
and you
you were um tasked with collecting
clandestinely the new Indonesian
economic figures.
Let's say you approach the Indonesian
Second Secretary for Economic Affairs.
You invite him to dinner. You invite him
to lunch. You strike up a friendship.
Your wives become friends. You spend
weekends together. But you realize that
he's not recruitable.
There's There's no hook that you can
that you can latch onto to recruit him
and get the documents.
What do you do? And one of the other
applicants raised his hand and he said,
"You double down and you take him to
more dinners and you you know, buy him
gifts." And
a woman raised her hand and she said,
"Maybe you can work it through the
wives. Maybe if if the wives become even
closer." And I raised my hand and I
said,
"You break into the Indonesian Embassy
and you steal it." And the instructor
said, "That's exactly what you do.
You break into the embassy and you steal
it." Well,
a normal person isn't going to break
into a foreign embassy to steal
documents.
But a person with sociopathic tendencies
would.
And so when you've got
an organization that is full of people
with sociopathic sociopathic tendencies,
but led by those handful of sociopaths
who slip through the process and rise to
the top by climbing on the backs of
their co-workers,
then you're going to have an
organization that commits crimes all the
time.
And I fear that that's what it is. Does
the CIA uh participate in the
distribution of drugs, controlled
dangerous substances?
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> I believe that the answer is yes. And
and I I paused because I'm sorry to even
have to say those words out loud. After
I left the CIA and when I decided to
return to government, I was the senior
investigator on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee. Uh it was chaired
at the time by John Kerry. And I did a
study
uh on the Afghan heroin poppy crop.
Afghanistan at the time produced 93% of
the world's heroin.
Now, when the Taliban were in power,
they produced 0% of the world's heroin.
So, I went to
Bagram Air Base
and flew from there to Well, first to
Kandahar and then to Lashkar Gah, which
is the capital of Helmand province, the
center of the heroin poppy cultivation
area.
And I went to speak I just went out into
the fields with a security team and a
translator and I happened upon
a poppy farmer.
And I asked him what, in retrospect, was
a silly question.
I said, "Instead of all this poppy, why
don't you Why don't you grow things that
have two growing seasons, like tomatoes
or onions or pomegranates?"
And he got a little angry and he said,
"The Americans told me in 2001 that if I
told them where the Arabs were, I could
grow all the poppy I wanted." And I
said, "What Americans told you you could
grow poppy?"
And as soon as the words came out of my
mouth, my military minder said that it
was too dangerous to remain here and he
physically pulled me back to the Jeep
and we went back to the base to fly back
to to Bagram.
Well, I wrote this up and I sent the
paper before I gave it to Senator Kerry,
I sent it to a friend of mine in the
DEA.
And I said, "Tell me if you think I'm
crazy with this paper." So, a few days
later he called me and he said, "Buddy,
you know you're never going to get this
published, right?"
And I said, "Why? Everything I said in
it is true."
And he said, "Afghanistan produces 93%
of the world's heroin.
But all of that heroin goes to Russia
and Iran and we want them to be addicted
to heroin. It weakens their societies,
just like the Chinese want us to be
addicted to fentanyl. You're never going
to get it published." And sure enough, a
few days later Senator Kerry comes to my
office and he says, "Listen, that that
paper that you're doing on on heroin,
yeah, we're not going to publish that
paper."
And so, it died a very quiet death. My
bottom line being,
we should have learned a lesson in the
1980s with cocaine coming from Nicaragua
out of the Iran-Contra war,
we didn't learn the lesson.
And then we ended up supporting the
heroin crop the heroin poppy crop in
Afghanistan.
20 years later. It was wrong then and
it's wrong now. Here's one of your
former colleagues, the very well-known
Jack Devine,
on this very subject, Chris. Didn't the
CIA itself once facilitate the movement
of drugs into the United States for some
CIA-designated
better purpose? Let me not Let me not
equivocate. That is absolutely
100% nonsense. The CIA never ever
transported drugs into the United States
or had anything to do with I spent all
my career beating the living daylight
out of
>> the CIA then looked the other way
while this happened so that the kingpins
behind the delivery of the drugs would
cooperate with the CIA. We all know
that, Jack. Gooey? I have no I have no
supporting evidence and I would like to
see
your and your team's supporting
evidence. We don't work with drug
traffickers. Who told me this nonsense?
>> [laughter]
>> Did he forget that Manuel Noriega, one
of the most notorious drug traffickers
in the Western Hemisphere, was a paid
CIA source for decades?
Listen, that's a dark time in the CIA's
history, but it needs to it needs to
address the issue truthfully.
The truth is that there were two
different groups of Contra rebels in
Nicaragua at the time. One, the CIA was
working directly with. The other, the
CIA was working tangentially with. It
was that second group that was sending
cocaine to the United States in exchange
for cash and for arms,
even if it was indirectly,
from the CIA. Listen, there was no such
thing as crack cocaine in the United
States until the CIA allowed cocaine
into the country in the mid-1980s that
was that was turned into crack cocaine
in a chemical refining process. They
should just come clean with it and be
done with it. It's historical at this at
this point. Just be honest about it.
Does the CIA trust the Israeli Mossad?
Yes and no.
On a person-to-person basis, no. It
doesn't trust the Israeli Mossad because
the CIA Every CIA officer knows that the
that the Mossad is spying on the United
States. And so, we have a a very large
and very active counterintelligence
center in the CIA whose job it is to
make sure that everything is on the up
and up inside the building and among its
officers. One of the the gravest threats
that we face is the threat of Israeli
spying.
On the other hand, when it comes to
operational issues, for example,
standing up against terrorist groups,
sure, the Mossad is is brutal, it's
well-trained, it's well-funded, it's
willing to jump into the fight with both
feet. So, on that one hand, sure, the
relationship is very close. On the other
hand, we always have to be wary of the
Mossad because we are their targets as
well as others.
Does the Mossad spy on the president of
the United States, on the White House?
I would have to assume that it does.
You know, just like in the in the Ed
Snowden revelations, people were
appalled that we were intercepting
Angela Merkel's cell phone. Angela
Merkel was at the time the Chancellor of
Germany. Well, you know, that's that's
what we do. We we intercept the
communications of foreign leaders.
There's no reason to think that the
Israelis aren't doing exactly the same
thing.
Tell me about the
part of the CIA that has become almost a
private army
for the president of the United States.
Yeah, this is a a decidedly post-9/11
development where the CIA makes such
broad and and wide use of contractors
that
I would I would guess there are probably
more contractors today than there are
CIA
uh
officials, CIA officers. And so, you
know, when you're using these
contractors, things like whatever
Blackwater is calling itself these days,
uh the president can use these groups or
the CIA can use these groups and give
the president an extra level of
deniability.
And so, you know, we see,
for example, news reports of
a boatload of idiots washing up on shore
in in Venezuela and being immediately
arrested. Well, none of them were CIA
officers.
Many of them claimed to be on the CIA's
payroll. I think they probably were.
And uh that's what happens when
when you carry out ill-conceived
operations using ill-prepared people for
for policy goals that have not been
fully thought out. And then you have to
start worrying about a prisoner
exchange.
Wow.
What would you do if you could reform
the CIA
just like that?
Well, there there's a lot that I would
do, but what I would do at the very
beginning was would be to absolutely
forbid CIA officers from becoming media
personalities until after a cooling-off
period. You know, if you are a senior
government official, you cannot become a
lobbyist until after an 18-month
cooling-off period.
I hate that somebody can be the CIA
director or the director of national
intelligence, leave on a Friday, and
then on Monday
they're [clears throat]
they're on MSNBC or on CNN as a paid
contributor. That doesn't make any
sense. And at the very least,
when you leave the CIA,
if you're not working on a classified
contract, you should not have a security
clearance.
How is it that it's permissible for
senior intelligence service retirees to
then go on as paid consultants uh
at these at these uh
cable news outlets
and they still have their security
clearances, they still have access to
classified information. And we're
supposed to just trust that they don't
mix classified information in with their
punditry.
Uh
another thing that I would do is we have
to address this issue of weaponization
immediately.
Uh I'm not exactly sure how to do that
yet. I'm actually thinking of something
to put down on paper. But but to
weaponize an organization like the CIA
or the FBI against a person whose
politics you don't like
or whose position on on some issue you
don't like is is un-American and should
be impermissible. The um
charter of the CIA
prohibits it from engaging in domestic
law enforcement or domestic
surveillance.
Two
um
former governors, I won't tell you what
states they're they're not contiguous to
each other,
uh told me a similar story that in the
early days of their governorship in
their respective state houses,
uh an assistant came and said,
"So-and-so
wants to see you." Who is he? "Well, we
don't know, but he works in the
building."
"All right, let me see him." And
so-and-so basically said, "I work for
the CIA." And both these governors said,
"Get the hell out." And the guy said,
"Well, I'll go, but I'll be replaced by
somebody who won't introduce himself to
you."
Does that surprise you? Does that strike
you as likely true? I know both of these
former governors. They repeated the
story to me several times.
I believe that. The CIA has a very, very
long reach.
Uh look at Hollywood uh movies.
Not only is there an office within the
CIA's office of public affairs, whose
job it is to work with Hollywood film
studios so that every TV series that
mentions the CIA, every every movie that
mentions the CIA delivers a pro-CIA
message. The FBI's been doing it since
the '50s. The CIA was a little bit late
to the game. Look at universities.
Uh when CIA officers were not allowed to
sort of infiltrate American universities
anymore and recruit uh young people to
join the CIA, they just started doing it
overtly. It's It's called the uh
scholar-in-residence program. Mhm.
>> And so, if you are a a CIA officer,
you've done your 30 years, you're going
to retire and go back home to, let's
say, Indiana,
they offer you a position. How about if
you go to Indiana University, you teach
some meaningless class like espionage in
Soviet literature, but really you're
there to be a spotter looking for people
who might be good CIA officers. So,
instead of hiding it, they just do it
out in the open.
Uh we also know, thanks to the the
Twitter revelations, uh Matt that Matt
Taibbi uh uh exposed, that there were
active-duty
CIA and FBI officers in place at
Twitter, at Facebook, all over the
social media platforms. Why? For what
reason? And why would they be undercover
in positions like that? And why would
active-duty officers be in those
positions? Because they're spying on
Americans. That's why.
So, last uh subject, the uh CIA was
created by the National Security Act of
1947,
uh which was signed into law by then
President Harry Truman.
Uh Truman insisted on the two
restrictions that I told you about, no
law enforcement, no domestic spying.
Uh 16 years later in 1963,
he published a an op-ed. This is a
former president of the United States.
You probably know this story, in the
Washington Post. In those days,
newspapers had two editions, a morning
edition and an afternoon edition.
And in the morning edition of this uh
particular day, his piece said, "It was
a damn fool mistake that I made, and if
I'd known what the CIA was going to do,
I never would have signed into law, and
it should be disbanded."
In the evening edition, that op-ed by
the former president of the United
States did not appear.
Does that surprise you?
No.
No, uh it's sickens me, certainly, but
it doesn't surprise me. Uh
President Truman was one of those rare
straight-talkers uh in modern American
history. And
he watched [snorts]
the CIA became the
the the monster that it became. Truman
believed at the time that it was
involved in the Kennedy assassination.
Truman knew there was no such thing at
the time as as an oversight committee on
Capitol Hill. The oversight committees
didn't come until 1976.
Um Eisenhower believed the CIA was out
of control, also. And he was one of the
CIA's greatest supporters through the
1950s. [clears throat]
But even he recognized what the CIA had
become.
That that's why I I really believe, and
I think President Trump also believes,
that it it needs to be torn down to its
studs and rebuilt.
And as difficult as it might be, it
needs to be a law-abiding
organization.
Deep down, I personally believe, Judge,
that we don't need to have a CIA. Uh
we already have analysis being done by
the State Department's Bureau of
Intelligence and Research. We have uh a
a group at the Pentagon called Defense
Human Services recruiting spies to steal
secrets.
We have DARPA and NSA and others working
on advanced technologies.
Why Why have a CIA if you can't control
it? Or why have a CIA if the overseers
on Capitol Hill, who are supposed to be
overseeing it and making sure that it
operates within the confines of the law,
are really little more than cheerleaders
for the CIA?
>> Right. They're called regulatory
regulatory capture when the entity being
regulated has captured its its
regulators. John, why don't you put this
in a book, or are you working on a book
on all this?
>> Well, I I'm proud to say that I I am.
I'm writing a paper about it right now.
And uh a dear friend of mine, uh Bruce
Fein, and I have been talking about this
book for 10 years. We're finally going
to start putting pen to paper in the
coming couple of weeks. Uh Bruce uh is a
lawyer and one of the greatest defenders
of the Bill of Rights in the country
today.
>> He is. Yes. John Kiriakou, you're a
great man, a genuine American hero.
Thank you for all the work you've done.
I hope you'll come and visit with us
again. Oh, Judge, I'm I'm a fanboy of
yours. So, uh that answer is yes. All
right. Thank you. All the best.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Coming up
tomorrow, uh Tuesday at 8:00 in the
morning, Ambassador Charles Chas
Freeman. At 11:00 in the morning, uh
Colonel Douglas Macgregor. At 1:00 in
the afternoon, Professor John
Mearsheimer. At 2:00 in the afternoon,
Matt Hoh. At 3:00 in the afternoon,
Karen Kwiatkowski. Join us on Paul Jay
for Judging Freedom.